Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- Manufacturers' Record, 1896-1897 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1896; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.20 (1896: Dec. 11)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1896; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.21 (1896: Dec. 18)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1896; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.22 (1896: Dec. 25)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.23 (1897: Jan. 1)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.24 (1897: Jan. 8)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.25 (1897: Jan. 15)
  - Item 14: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.26 (1897: Jan. 22)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1897: Jan. 29)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.2 (1897: Feb. 5)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1897: Feb. 12)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1897: Feb. 19)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1897: Feb. 26)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1897: Mar. 5)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1897: Mar. 12)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.8 (1897: Mar. 19)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.9 (1897: Mar. 26)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1897: Apr. 2)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.11 (1897: Apr. 9)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.12 (1897: Apr. 16)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31:no.13 (1897: Apr. 23)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.14 (1897: Apr. 30)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.15 (1897: May 7)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.16 (1897: May 14)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.17 (1897: May 21)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.18 (1897: May 28)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.19 (1897: June 4)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.21 (1897: June 11)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.22 (1897: June 18)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.23 (1897: July 2)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.24 (1897: July 9)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.25 (1897: July 16)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.26 (1897: July 23)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1897: July 25)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1897: July 30)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.2 (1897: Aug. 6)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.3 (1897: Aug. 13)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1897: Aug. 20)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1897: Aug. 27)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1897: Sept. 3)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1897: Sept. 10)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.8 (1897: Sept. 17)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.9 (1897: Sept. 24)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.10 (1897: Oct. 1)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.11 (1897: Oct. 8)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1897: Oct. 15)
  - Item 14: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1897: Oct. 15). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.13 (1897: Oct. 22)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1897-1898 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.14 (1897: Oct. 29)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.15 (1897: Nov. 5)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.16 (1897: Nov. 12)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.17 (1897: Nov. 19)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.18 (1897: Nov. 16)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.19 (1897: Dec. 3)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.20 (1897: Dec. 10)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.21 (1897: Dec. 17)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.22 (1897: Dec. 24)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1897; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.23 (1897: Dec. 31)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.24 (1898: Jan. 7)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.25 (1898: Jan. 14)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.32:no.26 (1898: Jan. 21)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1898: Jan. 28)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1898: Feb. 4)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1898: Feb. 11)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1898: Feb. 18)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.5 (1898: Feb. 25)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.6 (1898: Mar. 4)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.7 (1898: Mar. 11)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.8 (1898: Mar. 18)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.9 (1898: Mar. 25)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1898: Apr. 1)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.11 (1898: Apr. 8)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1898: Apr. 15)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.33:no.13 (1898: Apr. 22)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.14 (1898: Apr. 29)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.15 (1898: May 6)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.16 (1898: May 13)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.17 (1898: May 20)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.18 (1898: May 27)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.19 (1898: June 3)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.20 (1898: June 10)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.21 (1898: June 17)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.22 (1898: June 24)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.23 (1898: July 1)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.24 (1898: July 8)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.25 (1898: July 15)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.33:no.26 (1898: July 22)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.1 (1898: July 29)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.2 (1898: Aug. 5)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.3 (1898: Aug. 12)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.4 (1898: Aug. 19)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.5 (1898: Aug. 26)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.6 (1898: Sept. 2)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.7 (1898: Sept. 9)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.8 (1898: Sept. 16)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.9 (1898: Sept. 23)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.10 (1898: Sept. 30)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.11 (1898: Oct. 7)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.12 (1898: Oct. 14)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.34:no.13 (1898: Oct. 21)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1898-1899 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.14 (1898: Oct. 28)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.15 (1898: Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.16 (1898: Nov. 11)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.17 (1898: Nov. 18)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.18 (1898: Nov. 25)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.19 (1898: Dec. 2)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.20 (1898: Dec. 9)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.21 (1898: Dec. 16)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.22 (1898: Dec. 23)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1898; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.23 (1898: Dec. 30)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.24 (1899: Jan. 6)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.25 (1899: Jan. 13)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.26 (1899: Jan. 20)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.1 (1899: Jan. 27)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.2 (1899: Feb. 3)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.3 (1899: Feb. 10)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.4 (1899: Feb. 17)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.5 (1899: Feb. 24)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.6 (1899: Mar. 3)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.7 (1899: Mar. 10)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.8 (1899: Mar. 17)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.9 (1899: Mar. 24)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.10 (1899: Mar. 31)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.11 (1899: Apr. 7)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.12 (1899: Apr. 14)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.13 (1899: Apr. 21)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.14 (1899: Apr. 28)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.15 (1899: May 5)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.16 (1899: May 12)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.17 (1899: May 19)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.18 (1899: May 26)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.19 (1899: June 2)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.20 (1899: June 9)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.21 (1899: June 16)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.22 (1899: June 23)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.23 (1899: June 30)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.24 (1899: July 7)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.25 (1899: July 14)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35:no.26 (1899: July 21)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.1 (1899: July 29)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.2 (1899: Aug. 4)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1899: Aug. 11)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.4 (1899: Aug. 18)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.5 (1899: Aug. 25)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.6 (1899: Sept. 1)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.7 (1899: Sept. 8)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.8 (1899: Sept. 15)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.9 (1899: Sept. 22)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.10 (1899: Sept. 29)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.11 (1899: Oct. 6)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.12 (1899: Oct. 13)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.36:no.13 (1899: Oct. 20)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1899-1900 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.14 (1899: Oct. 27)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.15 (1899: Nov. 3)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.16 (1899: Nov. 9)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.17 (1899: Nov. 16)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.18 (1899: Nov. 23)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.19 (1899: Nov. 30)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.20 (1899: Dec. 7)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.21 (1899: Dec. 14)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.22 (1899: Dec. 21)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1899; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.23 (1899: Dec. 28)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.24 (1899: Jan. 4)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.25 (1899: Jan. 11)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.26 (1899: Jan. 18)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.1 (1900: Jan. 25)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.2 (1900: Feb. 1)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.3 (1900: Feb. 8)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.4 (1900: Feb. 15)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.5 (1900: Feb. 22)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.6 (1900: Mar. 1)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.7 (1900: Mar. 8)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.8 (1900: Mar. 15)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.9 (1900: Mar. 22)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.10 (1900: Mar. 29)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.11 (1900: Apr. 5)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.12 (1900: Apr. 12)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.13 (1900: Apr. 19)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.14 (1900: Apr. 26)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.15 (1900: May 3)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.16 (1900: May 10)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.17 (1900: May 17)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.18 (1900: May 24)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.19 (1900: May 31)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.20 (1900: June 7)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.21 (1900: June 14)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.22 (1900: June 21)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.23 (1900: June 28)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.24 (1900: July 5)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.24 (1900: July 5). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.25 (1900: July 12)
  - Item 14: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.37:no.26 (1900: July 19)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1900: July 26)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.2 (1900: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.3 (1900: Aug. 9)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.4 (1900: Aug. 16)
  - Item 5: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.5 (1900: Aug. 23)
  - Item 6: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.6 (1900: Aug. 30)
  - Item 7: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.7 (1900: Sept. 6)
  - Item 8: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.8 (1900: Sept. 13)
  - Item 9: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.9 (1900: Sept. 20)
  - Item 10: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.10 (1900: Sept. 27)
  - Item 11: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.11 (1900: Oct. 4)
  - Item 12: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.12 (1900: Oct. 11)
  - Item 13: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.38:no.13 (1900: Oct. 18)
- Manufacturers' Record, 1900-1901 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.14 (1900: Oct. 25)
  - Item 2: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.15 (1900: Nov. 1)
  - Item 3: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.16 (1900: Nov. 8)
  - Item 4: Manufacturers' Record, 1900; Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.17 (1900: Nov. 15)